const INITIAL_sTATE = [
    {
        "answer": "Namibia",
        "options": [
            "Namibia",
            "Niger",
            "Chad",
            "Ghana"
        ],
        "question": "Windhoek is the capital of__________?",

    },
    {
        "answer": "Euro",
        "options": [
            "Zolty",
            "Peso",
            "Euro",
            "Escudo"
        ],
        "question": "The currency of portugal is__________?",
    },
    {
        "answer": "Almaty",
        "options": [
            "Astana",
            "Almaty",
            "Baku",
            "Tashkent"
        ],
        "question": "Which of the following city served as capital of Kazakhstan till 1997?",

    },
    {
        "answer": "North Atlantic Ocean",
        "options": [
            "North Atlantic Ocean",
            "South Atlantic Ocean",
            "Pacific Ocean",
            "Arabian Sea"
        ],
        "question": "Bermuda Triangle is located in__________?",

    },
    {
        "answer": "Ramon Magsaysay Award",
        "options": [
            "Ramon Magsaysay Award",
            "Booker Prize",
            "Pulitzer Prize",
            "None of them"
        ],
        "question": "Which among the following is known as Asia a version of “Noble prize”?",

    },
    {
        "answer": "Geneva",
        "options": [
            "London",
            "Geneva",
            "Rome",
            "Paris"
        ],
        "question": "The headquarter of EFTA is in_____________?",

    },
    {
        "answer": "China",
        "options": [
            "Japan",
            "China",
            "South Koera",
            "None of These"
        ],
        "question": "Which country Built A 250-Acre Solar Farm Shaped Like A Giant Panda:",

    },
    {
        "answer": "White Bellbird",
        "options": [
            "Macaws",
            "Cockatoos",
            "White Bellbird",
            "None of these"
        ],
        "question": "________ is the World’s Loudest Bird",


    },
    {
        "answer": "Feb 29",
        "options": [
            "Feb 29",
            "Feb 28",
            "March 01",
            "Feb 01"
        ],
        "question": "_______ is known as leap day or leap year day",

    },
    {
        "answer": "China",
        "options": [
            "Japan",
            "Russia",
            "China",
            "None of These"
        ],
        "question": "Where is the World’s longest sea bridge ?",
        

    }
]


const reducer = (state = INITIAL_sTATE) => state;

export default reducer;
